quanki.com 2017-06-06

# Quanki.com - Privacy Policy.

Collection of Personal Information

Personal information is only obtained online if you supply it voluntarily, usually through some goverment agencies or third party information such as: applying online for a contest, answering online surveys, submitting a posting to a blog, forum, or review or registering for services, etc. You are not required to supply personal information to view the content on Quanki.com. You should also be aware that when you share personal information in public areas, this information may be seen and used by others, which our system in turn might pick up on. We urge you to exercise good judgment when sharing personal information in these areas.

Advertisements

We may use service providers to serve third party advertisements on Quanki. In serving advertisements, these providers may place cookies on your browser which may collect certain anonymous information about your visits to other websites or on Quanki.com. This information may include browser type, IP address, domain name and the name of the web page from which you entered such websites, web activity and the time of day. This information is used by these third parties to better understand and optimize their online advertising campaigns.

Terms of Use & Changes to this Privacy Policy

Your use of Quanki.com, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy and governed by our Terms of Use. We reserve the right to change and update the Policy, and these changes will be made when appropriate and in a timely manner. We encourage you to examine our Policy from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes we may have made.

Safeguards and Retention

We use physical, organizational and technological safeguards to protect your personal information against theft, loss or unauthorized access, use, modification, disclosure or disposal. Generally speaking, you can visit Quanki.com without revealing personal information. However, given that electronically submitted data is not 100% secure, we make no warranties as to the security of any personal information you submit online, which you do at your own risk.

Web Scraping/Harvesting

You may only use or reproduce the Content for your own personal and non-commercial use. The farming, scraping, data-mining, extraction or collection of the Content of Quanki.com in any form and by any means whatsoever is strictly prohibited. Furthermore, you may not mirror any material contained on Quanki.
